https://herb-e-concept.com/security-and-privacy-policy/

Security and Privacy Policy
Home•Security and Privacy Policy
Security and Privacy Policy
With the development of new communication tools, we consider that it is essential to protect your privacy. That’s why we are committed to respect the confidentiality of the personal information we collect.
Collection of Your Personal Information
We collect the following information:
Company name Last nameFirst nameMailing address Zip code EmailFax/phone numberCredit card numberGenderAge / Date of birth
The personal data that we collect is gathered using forms and through the interactivity established between you and our website. We also use, as mentioned in the following section, cookies and log files to gather information about you.
Forms and Interaction
Your personal data is collected using form:
Website registration formOnline ordering formContestsNewsletter registration formRegistration forms to receive a document, a webinar, a promotion
We use the collected data for the following purposes:
Order trackingInformation or promotional offersStatisticsContactWebsite Management (layout, structure)
We also collect your personal data through the interactivity established between you and our website as follows:
StatisticsContactWebsite Management (layout, structure)
We use the collected data for the following purposes:
CorrespondenceInformation or promotional offers
Cookies and Log Files
We collect some information by using log files and cookies. This includes mainly:
IP addressOperating system,Requested and visited pages,Hour and day of the connection
These types of files are used to:
Ensure improvement in service and a personalized welcomePersonalize consumer profileTrack orderAnalyze statisticsTo remember your favorite items or to save the products in your shopping cart for a future purchase.
If you post a comment on our website, you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
What We Collect and Store
During your visit we follow
Products you have searched: we use them, for example to display the products that you recently viewedLocalization, IP address and type of browser: we use them to estimate the tax and the shipping costs; Delivery address: we will ask to provide your address to estimate the shipping costs before you finalize your order and to send you your order!
We use cookies to store the content of your shopping cart while you are browsing our site. When you order from our website, we will ask you to provide us with your name, billing address, shipping address, email, phone number, payment details / credit card and possibly your account information such as username and password.
This information will be used:
To send information about your account and your order; To reply to your requests, including refunds and complaints;To proceed with the payment and to prevent;To set up your account;To comply with legal requirements such as the calculation of
sales tax;To improve our offersTo send you marketing messages if you want to
If you create an account, we store your name, address, email and phone number, which we use to automatically fill your order validation for your future orders.
We store your information for as long as we need for the purpose for which we are collecting them and using them. We do not have the legal obligation to keep longer.
For example, we store your order information for 10 years for tax and accounting purposes. This includes your name, email, billing address and delivery address.
We also store your comments if you choose to send them.
Who Can Access The Data?
The members of our team can access the information you provide. For example, administrators and the managers of the shop can access:
Your order details such as the products you bought, when and where the products were shippedYour customer information such as your name, email, billing and shipping information.
Our team can access this information to proceed with your order, to issue a refund and to help you.
Sharing of Personal Information
We share information with third parties that help us manage our orders and shop services.
Payments
We accept the following methods of payment: Stripe, PayPal and credit cards.
During the execution of the payments, some information will be sent to Stripe such as mandatory information about the payment: the total amount or the billing information.
Right of Veto and of Removal (Opt-out)
We are committed to offering you a right of veto and of removal regarding your personal information.
The right of veto is understood to mean the possibility offered to online visitors to refuse to have their personal information be used to certain ends outlined during collection.
The right of removal refers to the option offered to online visitors to choose that their personal information no longer be used in a mailing list, for example.
To use these rights please contact us at:
Address : address of Herb-e-Concept
Email : www.herb-e-concept.com
Phone number:
Website: « contact us» page
The personal data that we collect is stored in a secured environment. Our employees are required to respect the confidentiality of your information.
To ensure the security of your personal data, we use the following measures:
SSL Protocol (Secure Sockets Layer)SET (Secure Electronic Transaction)Access management – authorized personNetwork monitoring softwareData backupCreation of digital certificateUsername / PasswordFirewall
We are committed to maintain a high degree of confidentiality in integrating the latest technological innovations to ensure the confidentiality of your transaction. However, since no mechanism offers maximum security, a part of risk is always present when personal data is transmitted over the internet.
